{
	"Quiz1": [
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 1,
			"Question": "What is RAM?",
			"Choice1" : "A Truck",
			"Choice2" : " A Goat",
			"Choice3" : "Memory for your computer",
			"Answer": "Choice3",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num" : 2,
			"Question": "Where does RAM go?",
			"Choice1" : "On a Mountain",
			"Choice2" : "On the Road",
			"Choice3" : "Inside a computer",
			"Answer" : "Choice3",
			"Explanation" : ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 3,
			"Question" : "Which are  computer peripherals? (Choose All that Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Mouse",
			"Choice2" : "Flash Drive",
			"Choice3" : "An Add-on for your car",
			"Choice4" : "Keyboard",
			"Answer" : [1,2,4],
			"Explanation" : ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 4,
			"Question_1": "RAM stands for Random",
			"Question_2": "Memory",
			"Answer": "Access",
			"Explanation": ""
		}
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 5,
			"Question" : "Which are Access modifiers in Java (Choose All the Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Default",
			"Choice2" : "Private",
			"Choice3" : "Sergent",
			"Choice4" : "Protected",
			"Answer" : [1,2,4],
			"Explanation" : ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 6,
			"Question" : "Which are sorting algorithms (Choose All the Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Heap",
			"Choice2" : "Radix",
			"Choice3" : "Quick",
			"Choice4" : "Pop",
			"Answer" : [1,2,3],
			"Explanation" : ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 7,
			"Question_1": "The",
			"Question_2": "is the fastest sorting Algorithm",
			"Answer": "Quicksort",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 9,
			"Question" : "What Polymorphism?",
			"Answer": "Polymorphism is the ability of an object to take on many forms.",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 10,
			"Question": "Which is not a OOP Concepty",
			"Choice1" : "Abstraction",
			"Choice2" : " Multi-threaded",
			"Choice3" : "Encapsulation",
			"Answer": "Choice2",
			"Explanation": ""
		}


	],
	"Quiz2": [
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 1,
			"Question" : "What is an exception?",
			"Answer": "An exception is a problem that arises during the execution of a program.",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 2,
			"Question" : "What is Typecasting?",
			"Answer": "The concept of assigning a variable of one data type to a variable of another data type. It is not possible for the boolean data type.",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :3,
			"Question" : "Define Inheritance?",
			"Answer": "It is the process where one object acquires the properties of another.",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :4,
			"Question" : "What do you mean by a constructor?",
			"Answer": " A constructor is a method that has the same name as that of the class to which it belongs. As soon as a new object is created, a constructor corresponding to the class gets invoked. ",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 5,
			"Question": "What is Java (Check All that Applies",
			"Choice1" : "You can buy at Starbucks",
			"Choice2" : "Made from bean imported from Columbia",
			"Choice3" : "A OO high level general purpose programming language",
			"Answer" : "[3]",
			"Explanation" : ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 6,
			"Question": "What is a Java Package?",
			"Choice1" : "A Carton of Coffee",
			"Choice2" : " A single java file",
			"Choice3" : "A way of grouping a variety of classes and or interfaces togther.",
			"Answer": "Choice3",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 7,
			"Question": "What is a Microprocessor?",
			"Choice1" : "A small machine to shred cheese",
			"Choice2" : " A small machine to make coffee",
			"Choice3" : "A Digital device on a chip which performs basic operations.",
			"Answer": "Choice3",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :8,
			"Question" : "What is Cache Memory?",
			"Answer": "This is special very high-speed memory. It is used to speed up and synchronizing with high-speed CPU.",
			"Explanation": ""
		},
			

	]
}